Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part III: Guide to the Yale University Library Collection
Manuscripts and Archives
Henry A. Kissinger papers, part III
1938 - 2009
Bulk, 1977 - 2007
MS 2004
Kissinger, Henry
120.64 Linear Feet (282 boxes)
The papers consist of correspondence, memoranda, writings, photographs and other material that document the career of the diplomat, author and foreign policy expert and scholar Henry A. Kissinger, who served as United States Secretary of State from 1973 to 1977 and as Assistant to the President for National Security Affairs (National Security Advisor) from 1969 to 1975.
Manuscripts and Archives Sterling Memorial Library 128 Wall Street P.O. Box 208240 New Haven, CT 06520 Web: http://web.library.yale.edu/mssa Email: mssa.assist@yale.edu Phone: (203) 432-1735 Fax: (203) 432-7441
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Henry A. Kissinger, 2011.
Part I: Materials in Part I of the Kissinger Papers document his life from 1957 to 1982 and include copies of records from his government service. Part I was given to the Library of Congress by Henry A. Kisinger in 1976 and 1977, shortly after leaving office. Consult the Library of Congress (http://www.loc.gov/rr/mss/) for further information.
Part II is comprised of materials that are owned either by the Library of Congress or Yale University (Yale) and document Dr. Kissinger’s pre-government, government and post-government careers. When they were in Dr. Kissinger’s possession, the papers formed an integrated collection. To maintain that integrity, as well as increase access to these materials, the two institutions agreed to a joint project undertaken by Yale to arrange, describe and digitize them. Each institution now holds both paper and digital copies of Part II. The work was funded by Charles Johnson, Yale class of 1954, and Nicholas Brady, Yale Class of 1952.
Part III: Materials in Part III were originally maintained by Dr. Kissinger’s staff. They primarily document his post-government years. They were gifted to Yale in 2011.
Information about Access
Series IV, VI, VII, and VIII are open for research.
Access to Series I, II, and V requires written permission of Henry A. Kissinger or his designee, during his lifetime and for five years from the date of Dr. Kissinger's death, after which access is unrestricted.
Researchers must use the online access system for the digital version of this collection to submit their requests for permission from Kissinger. The portal to the digital collection provides researchers further instructions for requesting access and permissions, see http://web.library.yale.edu/digital-collections/kissinger-collection.
Series III is restricted for twenty-five years from the last date of creation (of all documents in a folder) or five years after Kissinger’s death, whichever comes later.
Researchers may not request access to the documents in Series III; the documents will be automatically opened to researchers as restrictions expire.
Information about Access
The entire collection has been digitized. As per repository policy, researchers must use the digital copies instead of the originals.
Alternative Formats
The entire collection is available in digital form through Yale University Library.
Associated Materials
Associated material: Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part I are located at the Manuscripts Division, Library of Congress.
Related material: Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part II (MS 1981).
Biographical / Historical
Henry Alfred Kissinger was born Heinz Alfred Kissinger on May 27, 1923, in Fürth, Germany, and immigrated to the United States in 1938. After studying at Harvard University, he joined the faculty there as a member of the Department of Government and made a reputation for his scholarly work on international affairs, which included his best-selling book Nuclear Weapons and Foreign Policy, published in 1957. He served as assistant to the president for national security affairs (national security advisor) from 1969 to 1975 and as Secretary of State from 1973 to 1977 under presidents Richard Nixon and Gerald Ford. In office, he was known especially for his work on normalizing relations with China, detente with the Soviet Union, peace negotiations for the Vietnam War and his Middle East shuttle diplomacy. After leaving office, Kissinger remained an influential author and commentator on foreign affairs and founded the international consulting firm Kissinger Associates.
Chronology
1923 Born in Fürth, Germany, to Louis and Paula (Stern) Kissinger
1938 Immigrated to the United States
1940 Enrolled in City College of New York
1943-1946 Served in U.S. Army
1946-1947 Civilian instructor, European Command Intelligence School, Germany
1949 Married Ann Fleischer (divorced 1964)
1950 Completed Bachelors of Arts, Harvard University
1951-1958 Founder and editor of Confluence
1952-1969 Director, International Seminar, Harvard University
1954 Completed PhD, Harvard University
1954-1969 Faculty member, Department of Government, Harvard University
1955-1956 Director, Study Group on Nuclear Weapons and Foreign Policy, Council on Foreign Relations
1956-1958 Director, Special Studies Project, Rockefeller Brothers Fund
1957 Published Nuclear Weapons and Foreign Policy
1957-1969 Faculty member, Center for International Affairs, Harvard University
1958-1969 Director, Defense Studies Program, Harvard University
1959 Resigned U.S. Army reserve commission Daughter Elizabeth born
1961 Son David born
1965 Published The Troubled Partnership: A Reappraisal of the Atlantic Alliance
1969-1975 Assistant to the President for National Security Affairs
1973-1977 Secretary of State
1974 Married Nancy Maginnes
1977 Joined the Center for Strategic and International Studies as a Counselor
1979 Published White House Years
1982 Founded Kissinger Associates, Inc. Published Years of Upheaval
1983-1985 Chairman, National Bipartisan Commission on Central America
1999 Published Years of Renewal
Scope and Contents
The papers consist of correspondence, memoranda, writings, photographs and other material that document the career of the diplomat, author and foreign policy expert and scholar Henry A. Kissinger, who served as United States secretary of state from 1973 to 1977 and as assistant to the president for national security affairs (national security advisor) from 1969 to 1975. These papers constitute Part III of a three part collection of Kissinger's personal papers. The Part III papers primarily document his career after he worked in government, as an influential author and commentator on international affairs and consultant. The Part III papers also contain material relevant to his years in office and career before government.
There are three major collections (Parts I-III) of Kissinger’s personal papers at the Yale University Library and the Library of Congress. Part I, maintained at the Library of Congress, consists of materials primarily documenting his government career and includes copies of records from his government service. Part II is maintained at both the Library of Congress and Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library. Part III, which this finding aid describes, is maintained at Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, and is comprised of materials mainly documenting Kissinger’s post-government career after 2000.
The papers in Part III primarily document Kissinger’s professional life from 2001 to 2007 although Part III also contains a number of files related to Kissinger’s government service and early career. The three Parts of the Henry A. Kissinger papers complement and overlap each other in numerous ways which the finding aids for each Part describe in greater detail. The Provenance section of this finding aid provides more information about the division of the papers into the three Parts. The Part III papers to a great extent serve as a supplement to the materials found in Part II. The correspondence files continue into the years 2001 to 2007 the series of professional and personal correspondence found in Part II. Likewise, the photographs series extend coverage of his career and social activities into 2006.
For documenting Kissinger’s government service, Part III materials are a significant supplement to Part I and Part II materials and to the official records of Kissinger’s government service found at the National Archives and Records Administration (NARA). Of particular note among the subject files (Series II) are a set of Nixon tapes partial transcripts which recount Kissinger’s conversations captured by the White House taping system from 1971 to 1973. The subject files also include a small number of memoranda of conversation with journalists and business and church leaders from 1971 to 1974. Series IV consists of a substantial, but incomplete, collection of copies of Kissinger’s telephone conversation transcripts from 1969 to 1974 from the Nixon Presidential Library. These invaluable transcripts document virtually every aspect of his foreign policy work for the Nixon administration. A small amount of the correspondence in Series I and a substantial portion of the photographs in Series VII date from Kissinger’s time in office.
In conjunction with Part II, the Part III papers document Kissinger’s career after he left office in 1977. The papers do not include files from his international consulting firm, Kissinger Associates, which he founded in 1982. The papers, however, do provide insight into his dealings with the international business community and foreign governments, primarily through correspondence and photographs. Additional material documents Kissinger’s work as an author and prominent commentator on international affairs, especially in Series II and V, which include research files from his books White House Years (1979), Diplomacy (1994), and Years of Renewal (1999) and an extensive collection of drafts of his syndicated articles. Part III also provides a limited amount of material on Kissinger’s family and social life, mainly through correspondence and photographs.
Part III materials relevant to Kissinger’s youth and early career are very limited and consist primarily of a copy of the final version of his undergraduate thesis at Harvard University and a small number of photographs.
Arrangement
The papers are arranged in eight series: I. Correspondence, 1941-2009. II. Subject files, 1958-2007. III. Restricted files, 1947-2006. IV. Telephone conversation transcript copies, 1969-1974. V. Writing and research materials, 1950-2006. VI. Cartoons and graphic materials, circa 1969-1989. VII. Photographs, 1938-2009. VIII. Moving images and sound recordings, 1976-1997.
Access Terms
United States -- Foreign relations -- 1969-1974.; United States -- Foreign relations -- 1974-1977.; United States -- Foreign relations -- Soviet Union.; United States -- Foreign relations -- China.; Diplomats -- United States.; Kissinger, Henry; Ford, Gerald R.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous); National Security Council (U.S.); United States. Department of State
Collection Contents
- Correspondence, 1941 - 2009; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  The correspondence files document Kissinger’s post-government career, primarily from 2001 to 2007. The files include correspondence from Kissinger’s Washington, DC, and New York offices. For the New York office correspondence from 2001, see the Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part II. An attempt has been made to remove the large number of duplicates from these overlapping correspondence files. Most material is filed under the last name of the correspondent or organization name, but a small amount is filed under the names of countries or other subject terms.
  The Washington and New York files contain incoming and outgoing letters, enclosures and printed e-mail that document Kissinger’s contacts with the public, friends, and foreign policy community including the press, business leaders, politicians, foreign officials, and academics. Many of the correspondents are prominent individuals in their fields, including heads of state and international celebrities, but the correspondence primarily concerns invitations, publications of interest to Kissinger, condolences to the families of deceased friends and colleagues, and various requests. Much of the correspondence is brief and formulaic, often involving a wide variety of non-government organizations, many outside the foreign policy community including the Boy Scouts of America and the Federation Internationale de Football Association (FIFA), with which he had an affiliation or which were seeking his support. Kissinger’s engagement with journalists and authors about his policy work as a diplomat is reflected in scattered correspondence including exchanges with Alan M. Dershowitz, Marvin Kalb, and Walter Laqueur about Christopher Hitchins’ controversial writings about Kissinger, and letters with Marion Dönhoff in the 2001 Washington files. A small amount of international correspondence expressing support and sympathy for the United States after the 9/11 terrorist attacks can also be found in the 2001 Washington files.
  The White House personal files contain a portion, primarily the correspondence with individuals whose last name began with the letter N, of the set of White House correspondence found in Part II. The correspondence found here in Part III is missing from the Part II files.
  Arrangement
  Series I is arranged into three subseries: Washington, DC office, New York office, and White House personal file.
  Conditions Governing Access
  The papers are open with permission.
  - Washington, DC office
    - 2001
      - Ab, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Ac-Al, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Am-Ap, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Ar, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - As-Au, 2000 - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Ba, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Be, 2000 - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Bi, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Bl, 2000 - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Bo, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Br, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Bu-By, 1997 - 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Ca, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Ce, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Ch-Ci, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Cl, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Co [includes photograph], 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Cr-Cy, 1993 - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Da, 2000 - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - De, 2000 - 2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Di, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Do-Dy, 1999 - 2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Ea-Ep, 2000 - 2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Eq-Ew, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Fa-Fl, 2000 - 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Fo, 2000 - 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Fr-Fu, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Ga, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Ge-Gh, 2000 - 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Gi-Gl, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Go [includes photograph], 2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Gr, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Gu-Gy, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Ha, 2000 - 2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - He-Hi, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Ho, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Hu-Hy, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - I, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Ja-Ji, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Jo, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Ka-Ke, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Ki-Kl, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Ko, 1999 - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Kr-Ky [includes photograph], 2001 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - La, 2000 - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Le, 2000 - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Li-Lu, 2000 - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Ma, 2000 - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Mc, 2001 - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Me, 2000 - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Mi-My, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Na, 2000 - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Ne-Ni, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - No-Nu, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Ob-Ol, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Os-Ow, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Pa [includes photographs], 2000 - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Pe-Pl, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Po-Pr, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Q, 2000 - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Ra, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Re-Rh, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Ri, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Ro-Ru, 2000 - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Sa, 2000 - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Sc, 2000 - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Se-Sh, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Si-Sn, 2000 - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - So-Sp, 2000 - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - St-Sy, 2001 - 2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Ta-Te, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Th-Tu, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - U, 2000 - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Va-Ve, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Vo, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Wah-Wal, 1994 - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Wan-Wat, 2000 - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - We-Wh, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Wi, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Wo-Wu, 2000 - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Y, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Z, 2001 - 2002 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 2002
      - Ab-Al, 2001 - 2002 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Am, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - An-At, 2001 - 2002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Au-Bb, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Be-Bh, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Bi-Bl, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Bo, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Br, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Bu-By [includes photographs], 2002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Ca, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Cen-Chi, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Cho-Civ, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Cla-Coo, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Cou-Cut, 2001 - 2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Dal-Dek, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Del-Dis, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Do, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Dr-Dy, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Ea-Fc, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Fe-Fl, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Fo, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Fr-Fu, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Ga-Gh, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Gi-Gl, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Gol-Gra, 2002 - 2003 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Gre-Gut, 2001 - 2002 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Haa-Hal, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Ham-Hau, 2001 - 2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - He-Hi, 2001 - 2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Ho, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Hu-Hy, 1979, 2002; 2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - I, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - J, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Ka-Kl, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Ko-Ky, 1998 - 2002 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - La-Le, 2001 - 2003 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Li-Lu, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Ma [includes photograph], 2001 - 2002 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Mcc-Mer, 2001 - 2002 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Mes-Mit, 1970, 2002; 2002 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Mo-My, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - N, 2001 - 2003 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - O, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Pal-Pen, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Per-Pit, 2001 - 2002 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Pl-Pr, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Qa-Ri, 2000 - 2002 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Ro, 1948, 2002; 2002 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Ru, 2001 - 2002 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Sad-Sch, 2001 - 2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Sco-Sin, 2001 - 2002 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Sit-Sri, 2001 - 2002 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - St-Sy, 1975; 2001 - 2002 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Ta-Te, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Th-Ty, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - U-V, 1998 - 2002 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Wa, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - We-Wy, 1994 - 2002 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Y-Z, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 2003
      - Ab [includes photograph], 2003 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Ac-Al, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Am-An, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Ar, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - As-Az, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Ba, 2002 - 2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Be, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Bi, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Bl-Bm, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Bo, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Bra-Bre, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Bri-Brz, 2002 - 2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Bu, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Ca, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Ce, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Ch-Ci, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Cl, 2002 - 2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Coa-Coo, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Cor-Cox, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Cr-Cu, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Da, 2002 - 2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - De, 2002 - 2003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Di-Dj, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Do-Du, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Department of Defense, 2003 February-August (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Department of Defense, 2003 September-October (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Department of Defense, 2003 November-December (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - E, 2002 - 2003 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Fa-Fe [includes photograph], 2003 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Fi-Fo, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Fr-Fu, 2002 - 2003 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Ga, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Ge, 2002 - 2003 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Gi, 2002 - 2003 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Gl-Gn, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Go, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Gr, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Gu-Gy, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Ha, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - He-Hi [includes photograph], 2003 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Ho, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Hs-Hy, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Hamre, John J., 2003 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - I, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - J, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Kag-Kap, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Kar-Kha, 1962; 2003 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Ki, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Kl-Ko, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Kr-Ku, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - La, 2002 - 2003 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Le-Li, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Lo-Ly, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Ma, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Mac-Mar, 2002 - 2003 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Mas-Mcn, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Me-Mo, 2002 - 2003 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Mu-My, 2002 - 2003 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Na-Ne, 2001 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Ni-Ny, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - O, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Pa, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Pe-Pl, 2002 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Po-Pu, 2000 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Pentagon, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Q, 2002 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Ra-Rh, 2002 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Ric-Rog, 2002 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Roh-Rov, 2002 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Row-Ruh, 2002 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Rumsfeld, Donald, 2003 March-September (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Rumsfeld, Donald, 2003 October-December (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Sac-Sca, 2002 - 2003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Scha-Schn, 2001 - 2003 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Scho-Scow, 2002 - 2003 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Se-Sh, 2002 - 2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Si, 1990; 2003 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Sk-Sp, 1985 - 1986; 2003 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - St-Sy, 2002 - 2003 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Ta-To, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Tr, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - U, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - V, 2002 - 2003 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Wa, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - We-Wi, 2002 - 2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Wo, 2002 - 2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Wr-Wy, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Y, 2002 - 2003 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Z, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - 2004
      - Ab-Al, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Am-As, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - At-Az, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Ba-Be, 2003 - 2004 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Bi-Bm, 2003 - 2004 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Bo, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Bra-Bro, 2003 - 2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Bru-Bus, 2003 - 2004 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Ca, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Ce-Cl, 2004 - 2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Co, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Cr-Cu, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Cordesman, Anthony, 2004 January-September (Box 18, Folder 10)